mysimplifieds.com 2009-02-16

# mySimplifieds.com Malaysia: Privacy Policy

|    
---  
  | 

|   
---  
|  Privacy Policy  
---  
  
**mySimplifieds.com**

| 

PRIVACY POLICY  

---  
  
This Statement of Privacy applies to the web site of mySimplifieds.com, an online and mobile portal service provided by Kasatria Technologies Sdn. Bhd. (Company No.: 618655-V) (hereinafter known as “Kasatria Technologies”). As a media communications and internet based company which provides web services to the public, Kasatria Technologies is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following to fully understand our practices regarding the use of your personal information. By using mySimplifieds.com (the “Site”), you consent to the data practices described herein.

This policy applies specifically to your name, e-mail address, telephone number, and any other individually identifiable information which we collect from our users.  
  
WHAT WE COLLECT  

Kasatria Technologies’ general policy is to only collect individually identifiable information that is absolutely necessary for the transaction or useful for our own internal operations. During the registration process and creation of an account, for accountability purposes, we do require a user's e-mail address and mobile number. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, "Personal Data" shall include, where applicable, to your name, your company name, your contact details, your user identification and password to the Site, and all other information which may identify you or you as a class of persons. 

We record the e-mail addresses and messages of those who publish, post messages, photographs, communications and comments or feedback on the Site, or who communicate with us via e-mail. 

We also record aggregate information on what pages our users access or visit, information volunteered by users and merchants, such as survey information and/or Site registration data, and the e-mail address of merchants, buyers and sellers on the Site. 

We will also track certain particulars about you. This information includes the URL that you just came from (whether this URL is on our Site or not), which URL you next go to (whether this URL is on our Site or not), browser type, access times, the pages you visit and your IP address. Many sites automatically collect this information using widely available site web statistical tools.   
  
COOKIES  

We use cookies on our Site. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our Site. Most cookies are "session cookies", meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. However, if you click on the ‘Remember Me’ function, the cookie is stored on your hard drive and is not deleted at the end of the session. 

We let the advertisers on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not Kasatria Technologies’ Privacy Policy. Other companies do not have access to our cookies, and we do not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the other companies.   
  
WHAT WE DO WITH INFORMATION COLLECTED  

We collect and use your information to operate the Site and to deliver to you the services you have requested, including but not limited to the following : 

(i)                 customising the advertising and content you see;

(ii)               fulfil your requests for, or to inform you of, products and services;

(iii)             improve our services;

(iv)              contacting you;

(v)                billing you (where applicable);

(vi)              conduct research/surveys;

(vii)            provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients;

(viii)          resolve disputes and troubleshoot problems; and

(ix)              enforce our terms and conditions for using the Site.

We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of our business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your personally identifiable information (including but not limited to e-mail, name, address, telephone number and Identity Card number) is not transferred to the third party. We may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you e-mail or mobile message, provide customer support. These third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to us, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

We shall use all the information collected from you during the whole duration of your subscription to this Service (Collected Information) to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to statistically analyze site usage, to improve our content and product offerings and to customize our Site’s content, layout and service specifically for you. We may use your Collected Information to service your Account with us, including but not limited to investigating problems, resolving disputes and enforcing agreements with us. We do not sell, rent, trade or exchange any personally-identifying information of our Users. We may share certain aggregate information based on analysis of Collected Information with our partners, customers, advertisers or potential Users. We may use your Collected Information to execute marketing campaigns, promotions or advertising messages on behalf of third parties; however, in these circumstances, your Collected Information will not be disclosed to such third parties unless you respond to the marketing, promotion or advertising message.

We will disclose your information, without notice, when required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to : 

(i)                 conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on us or this Site;

(ii)               protect and defend the rights or property of Kasatria Technologies and this Site;

(iii)             enforce the terms and conditions of use of this Site;

(iv)              investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the personal safety of any person, or as otherwise required by law; and

(v)                act under exigent circumstances to protect the interests of our users, this Site or others.

Kasatria Technologies and our authorized third party partner(s) shall from time to time view and use the user’s identifiable information for any purpose whatsoever. 

We reserve the right to transfer information about you in the event we are acquired by or merged with another company.  
  
CREATING A PUBLIC PROFILE  

Under the “My Profile” feature, we give you an option to provide your contact numbers under the “Update Profile” page, containing personal information that you have volunteered so that other members or users in mySimplifieds.com and other public areas can make contact with you. Although entering profile information is not compulsory, adding more details will make it easier for prospects to get in touch with you. When you make a posting, the information will be made available to everyone, which may include users who are not logged in.

While participating in mySimplifieds.com or other public areas, we strongly advise you against giving out personally identifiable information to strangers online, which they may use for illegal or harmful purposes.   
  
YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION  

You can update or edit your personal information at any time by clicking on the “My Profile” link. 

We reserve the right to send you marketing communications and communications relating to the Services, such as service announcements, administrative messages and newsletters, from time to time. However, all communications sent via email will contain information on how to unsubscribe from that list. In the event that you receive an e-mail or mobile message that you think is unsolicited, please e-mail us at 

[feedback@mySimplifieds.com](mailto:feedback@mySimplifieds.com).   
  
AFFILIATED PARTNERS

We will establish relationships with other parties to offer you the benefit of other products and services which we ourselves do not offer. We offer you access to these other parties either through the use of hyperlinks to their sites from our Site, or through offering "affiliated partner" sites in which both ourselves and these other parties share the same uniform resource locator, domain name or pages within a domain name on the Internet. In some cases you may be required to submit information for purposes of registering or applying for products or services provided by such third parties or affiliated partners. The privacy policy of such other parties may differ from ours, and we may not have any control over the information that you submit to such third parties or affiliated partner sites. We therefore encourage you to read that policy before responding to any offers, products or services provided by such other parties.

MINORS

The Site and its contents are not intended to be targeted to minors under applicable law of Malaysia and we do not intend to sell any of our products or services to minors. If a minor has provided us with personal information without parental or guardian consent, the parent or guardian should contact us to remove the information.

SECURITY MEASURES

We employ commercially reasonable security methods to prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct use of information.

As a Registered User, your Registration Information, Publishing Information and Payment Information (if any) can be viewed and edited through your Account which is protected by Password. We recommend that you do not divulge your Password to anyone. Our personnel will never ask you for your Password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited e-mail. If you share a computer with others, you should not choose to save your log-in information (e.g., User ID and Password) on the computer. Remember to sign out of your Account and close your browser window when you have finished your session.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be perfectly secured. As a result, while we try to protect your information, no web site or company, including ourselves, can absolutely ensure or guarantees the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY  

We may, at our sole discretion, modify, update or revise this Privacy Policy at any time, without any notice, and you agree to be bound by these modifications or revisions. The amended terms and conditions shall automatically become effective upon posting on our Site. We shall indicate the latest Privacy Policy date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy for your easy reference. Your continued access to or use of this Site after such change shall constitute your 

(i)              acknowledgement of this Privacy Policy, as modified/revised from time to time; and 

(ii)            your consent to abide and be bound by this Privacy Policy, as modified/revised from time to time.   
  
This Privacy Policy, as modified/revised from time to time, is incorporated into and subject to the [Terms of Use](http://www.mysimplifieds.com/TermsOfUse.aspx) for the Services. 

We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how we are protecting your information. 

If you have any questions or concerns regarding these Terms of Service, please contact us at: 

Kasatria Technologies Sdn Bhd (618655-V)  
Unit 912, Block B2,   
Leisure Commerce Square   
46150 Bandar Sunway 

Tel: +603 78771560 / Fax: +603 58820309 / Email: 

|    

  |  |   |  |   |   
---|---|---|---
